<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart Reality Modules</string>
    <string name="no_notification_found">Currently there are no new notification.</string>
    <string name="no_internet">No Internet Connection</string>
    <item name="bound_observable" type="id" />

    <!-- REFER FRIEND-->
    <string name="refer_name">*Name</string>
    <string name="refer_mobile_number">*Mobile No.</string>
    <string name="refer_alt_mobile">Alternate Mobile No.</string>
    <string name="refer_email_id">Email ID</string>
    <string name="refer_project_interested_in">*Project Interested In</string>
    <string name="refer_dob">Date of Birth</string>
    <string name="refer_adderess">Address</string>
    <string name="refer_pincode">Pincode</string>

    <string name="enter_name">Enter Name</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_mobile_no">Enter Valid Mobile No.</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_alt_mobile_no">Enter Valid Alternative Mobile No.</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_email_id">Enter Valid Email ID</string>
    <string name="enter_dob">Enter Date Of Birth</string>
    <string name="enter_anniversary_dob">Enter Anniversary Date</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_pincode">Enter Valid Pin Code</string>
    <string name="data_error">Sorry for inconvenience. Please try again later</string>

    <!-- Strings related with About Us -->

    <string name="about_us_better_future">The Key To A Better Future</string>
    <string name="about_us_leadership">The Path Of Leadership</string>
    <string name="about_us_way_ahead">The Way Ahead</string>
    <string name="about_us_tc">Terms &amp; Condition</string>
    <string name="about_us_pp">Privacy Policy</string>


    <!--Strings related about details-->

    <string name="about_us_future">  <![CDATA[ <p>SPR is the leading real estate developer dedicated to the acquisition and development of residential and
            commercial projects in Tamil Nadu. Founded in 1972 by Prithviraj S Kawad to explore a plethora of opportunities across a full range of development capacities; SPR has consistently lived up to the commitment of delivering more than what delivering more than what is promised.</p>
          <p>Innovation is a key to our competitive differentiation and value proposition. We strive to surpass expected standards and set new ones through excellence in terms of scalability, flexibility and operational efficiency. Our efforts to differentiate ourselves by providing exceptional value has been recognised and acknowledged by the industry and our customers.</p>
          <p>We ventured into real estate with excellence in living as the key to a better future. Through our exceptional
            projects, we have now become a trusted source of innovation, expertise and passionate architecture.</p>
          <p>Today, under the leadership of Mr. Hitesh P Kawad, SPR is being taken to greater heights as we cross significant milestones in our journey of discovering endless possibilities of the growth ahead.</p>  ]]>
    </string>

     <string name="about_us_leaderships">  <![CDATA[ <p>As a forward-thinking leader, Mr. Hitesh brings with him a wealth of experience and knowledge of the Real Estate industry. His valuable experience, strong convictions, and thorough understanding based on the foundations of professionalism, integrity and expertise has driven SPR Group to reaching such great heights.</p>
        <p>As the real estate sector surpasses its traditional role as a builder towards offering a holistic package of end to end solutions for a home buyer, Mr. Hitesh has propelled SPR in adapting to the changing dynamics through a turn-around in corporate strategy by instilling a sense of purpose, unerring focus and conviction to strive for the best in every way.</p>
        <p>One of his greatest strengths is his ability to understand exactly what the customer wants – to think like they do, to understand things from their perspective, and sometimes even to anticipate their needs before they realize it themselves. This combination of intuition, insight and innovation has helped SPR deliver consistently in line with changing needs and put the customer first, always.</p> ]]>
     </string>

     <string name="about_us_terms">  <![CDATA[ <p>Please read the Terms & Conditions of use before accessing or using this website.</p>
        <p> By accessing or using this site you agree to be bound, without limitation or qualification, by these Terms & Conditions of use. If you do not accept any of the Terms & Conditions stated herein, please do not use this site. SPR Construction Private Limited may, in its sole discretion, modify or revise these Terms & Conditions at any time by updating this web page. You are bound by any such modification or revision.</p>
        <p> You may also read the Privacy Policy before using this site.  </p>
        <p> Warranty Disclaimer: SPR Construction Private Limited makes every effort to ensure the accuracy, accessibility, integrity and timeliness of this information. But SPR Construction Private Limited cannot and does not guarantee, and makes no warranties as to the above. SPR Construction Private Limited assumes no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of this site and further disclaims any liability of any nature for any loss howsoever caused in connection with using this website.</p>
        <p> Without prior notice SPR Construction Private Limited may make changes to these content at any time. The products and services mentioned on the website are subject to availability. Information on programs and details of services displayed on this website may vary or alter from the actual specifics; it is therefore strongly recommended that you contact SPR Construction Private Limited before making any decisions.</p>
        <p> Disclaimer – By entering this site you acknowledge and agree that your use is at your own risk and that none of the parties involved in creating, producing, or delivering this site is liable for any direct, incidental, consequential,</p>
        <p> indirect, or punitive damages, or any other losses, costs, or expenses or any kind (including legal fees, expert fees, or other disbursements) which may arise, directly or indirectly, through the access to, use of, or browsing of this site or through your downloading of any materials, data, text, images, video or audio from this site, including but not limited to anything caused by any viruses, bugs, human action or inaction or any computer system, phone line, hardware, software or program malfunctions, or any other errors, failures or delays in computer transmissions or network connections.
        Links to other sites – Although this site may be linked to other sites, SPR Construction Private Limited is not, directly or indirectly, implying any approval, association, sponsorship, endorsement, or affiliation with the linked site, unless specifically stated therein. By entering this site you acknowledge and agree that SPR Construction Private Limited has not reviewed all the sites linked to this site and is not responsible for the content of any off-site pages or any other site linked to this site. Your linking to any other off-site pages or other sites is at your own risk. SPR Construction Private Limited does not control the availability and content of services in those links and resources. Any concerns regarding any such services or resource, or any link thereto, should be directed to the respective service or resource. SPR Construction Private Limited does not endorse the content or material of the hyper links provided herein. Please take required permission from other websites and SPR Construction Private Limited for linking to this website.
        Termination of Access – SPR Construction Private Limited reserves the right to terminate your access to the website or any portion thereof at any time, without notice at it sole discretion.
        Indemnity – You agree to indemnify and hold harmless SPR Construction Private Limited, its parent companies, subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, directors, agents, employees, co-branders or other partners, and suppliers, from any claim, demand, action, or damage, including reasonable attorney’s fees, made by any third party due to, arising out of or related to your use of this website, your violation of the Terms & Conditions, any right of another, your connection to the website. </p>
        <p>Use – The user acknowledges that the use of the website by the user does not constitute a joint venture, partnership, employment or agency relationship between the user and SPR Construction Private Limited. You agree not to hold yourself as a representative, agent, or employee of SPR Construction Private Limited and SPR Construction Private Limited shall not be liable for any representation, act, or omission of the user.        </p>
        <p>Legal Jurisdiction – The Courts in Chennai alone will have exclusive jurisdiction in relation to all disputes which may arise out of or in connection with the use of the website The interpretation of these terms and conditions shall be construed in accordance with and governed by the laws of Union of India without giving effect to conflict of laws provision. Contacting SPR Construction Private Limited- By entering this site you acknowledge that this site is only for information purposes and you could contact us via using the “Contact Us” section on this website. But for all practical and legal purposes you are required to address your communication by certified mail to the below given address:</p>
        <b>SPR Construction Private Limited</b><br />
               <b> Registered Office:  </b><br />
                No.57, Narayana Mudali Street<br />
                Chennai 600079<br />
                Phone: +91 44 3728 3300<br /><br />
                <b>Corporate Office:</b><br />
                135, Sapna Trade Centre,<br />
                Poonamalee High Road,<br />
                Egmore, Chennai – 600084 <br />
                Phone: +91 44 3728 3300 <br />
                Website: www.sprindia.com
                 ]]>
     </string>

     <string name="about_us_privacy">  <![CDATA[
        <p>  This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.</p>
        <p>What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?</h2>
        <p>When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.</p>
        <p>When do we collect information?</p>
        <p>We collect information from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our site.</p>
        <p>How do we use your information?</p>
        <p>We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:</p>
        <p>How do we protect visitor information?</p>
        <p> Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.</p>
        <p>We use regular Malware Scanning.</p>
        <p>We do not use an SSL certificate</p>
        <span>We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like email addresses, or credit card numbers.</span>
        <p>Do we use ‘cookies’?</p>
        <p> We do not use cookies for tracking purposes    </p>
        <p>You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
        However, you can still place orders. </p>
        <p>Third-party disclosure</p>
        <p> We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.
        However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
        Third-party links.
        We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.</p>
        <p>Google</p>
        <p> Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en</p>
        <p> We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
        Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.</p>
        <p>We have implemented the following:</p>
        <p>  Demographics and Interests Reporting   </p>
        <p> We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. </p>
        <p> Opting out:
        Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.</p>
        <p>California Online Privacy Protection Act</p>
        <p>CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf</p>
        <p>  According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:</p>
        <p> Users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
        Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can be easily be found on the page specified above. Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:Users are able to change their personal information: By emailing us</p>
        <p> How does our site handle do not track signals?</p>
        <p> We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.    </h3>
        Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?</p>
        <p>  It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
        COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
        When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.
        We do not specifically market to children under 13.  </p>
        <p> Fair Information Practices
        The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.</p>
        <p>In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:</h2>
        <p>  We will notify the users via email
        We will notify the users via in-site notification
        Within 7 business days
        We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.</p>
        <p>   CAN SPAM Act
        The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. </p>
        <p>   We collect your email address in order to:</p>
        <p>If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at sales@sprosian.com and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.</p>
        <p> Contacting Us</p>
        <p>  If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below</p>
        <b>SPR Construction Private Limited</b><br />

                <b>Corporate Office:</b><br />
                135, Sapna Trade Centre,<br />
                Poonamalee High Road,<br />
                Egmore, Chennai –  600084 <br />
                Phone: +91 44 3728 3300 <br />

      ]]>
     </string>
    <string name="share_msg">Hi, just thought of sharing SPR App. Click on this link http://bit.ly/2jDOixX to get the app.</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="no_project_found">No Project Found</string>
    <string name="start_from">Starts From</string>
    <string name="about_project">About Project</string>
    <string name="amenities">Amenities</string>
    <string name="schedule_site_visit">Schedule Site Visit</string>
    <string name="online_blocking">Online Booking</string>
    <string name="project_images">PROJECT IMAGES</string>
    <string name="gallery">GALLERY</string>
    <string name="layout">LAYOUT</string>
    <string name="no_video_available">Video Not Available</string>
    <string name="no_360_video_available">360 View Is Not Available</string>
    <string name="server_unavailable">Server Unavailable</string>
    <string name="no_gallery_image_available">Gallery Images Not Available</string>
    <string name="site_visit_select_project">Select Project Name</string>
    <string name="site_visit_schedule_date">*Schedule Date</string>
    <string name="site_visit_schedule_time">*Schedule Time</string>
    <string name="site_visit_pickup_home">Pick up from home</string>
    <string name="site_visit_set_time">*Set Time</string>
    <string name="site_visit_enter_address">*Enter Address</string>
    <string name="site_visit_city">City</string>
    <string name="date_should_greater">You cannot select previous Date</string>
    <string name="schedule_time_should_greater">You can not select past time</string>
    <string name="select_site_visit_schedule_date">Select schedule date</string>
    <string name="pickup_time_less_than_schedule_time">Pickup time should be less than Visit time</string>
    <string name="select_site_visit_schedule_time">Select Schedule Time</string>
    <string name="select_site_visit_set_time">Select Pick up Time</string>
    <string name="enter_address">Enter Address</string>
    <string name="no_layout_image_available">Layout images not available.</string>

</resources>
